[
    {
        "question_id": 1,
        "questionText": "Which of the following does TypeScript use to specify types?",
        "option_id": 1,
        "text": ":",
        "correct": 1
    },

  {
      "question_id": 1,
      "questionText": "Which of the following does TypeScript use to specify types?",
      "option_ids": "1,2,3,4",
      "option_texts": ":,;,!,&",
      "option_correct": "1,0,0,0"
  },
  {
      "question_id": 2,
      "questionText": "Which of the following is NOT a type used in TypeScript?",
      "option_ids": "5,6,7,8",
      "option_texts": "number,string,boolean,enum",
      "option_correct": "0,0,0,1"
  },
  {
      "question_id": 3,
      "questionText": "How can we specify properties and methods for an object in TypeScript?",
      "option_ids": "9,10,11,12",
      "option_texts": "Use classes.,Use interfaces.,Use enums.,Use async/await.",
      "option_correct": "0,1,0,0"
  },
  {
      "question_id": 4,
      "questionText": "How else can Array<number> be written in TypeScript?",
      "option_ids": "13,14,15,16",
      "option_texts": "@number,number[ ],number!,number?",
      "option_correct": "0,1,0,0"
  },
  {
      "question_id": 5,
      "questionText": "In which of these does a class take parameters?",
      "option_ids": "17,18,19,20",
      "option_texts": "constructor,destructor,import,subscribe",
      "option_correct": "1,0,0,0"
  },
  {
      "question_id": 6,
      "questionText": "Which is NOT an access modifier?",
      "option_ids": "21,22,23,24",
      "option_texts": "private,protected,public,async",
      "option_correct": "0,0,0,1"
  },
  {
      "question_id": 7,
      "questionText": "Which keyword allows us to share information between files in TypeScript?",
      "option_ids": "25,26,27,28",
      "option_texts": "import,export,async,constructor",
      "option_correct": "0,1,0,0"
  },
  {
      "question_id": 8,
      "questionText": "Which is an array method to generate a new array based on a condition?",
      "option_ids": "29,30,31,32",
      "option_texts": "filter,map,async,enum",
      "option_correct": "1,0,0,0"
  },
  {
      "question_id": 9,
      "questionText": "How is a property accessible within a class?",
      "option_ids": "33,34,35,36",
      "option_texts": "Using this.propertyName,Accessors,Destructuring,Arrow function",
      "option_correct": "1,0,0,0"
  }
]
